The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
We just have to follow the floating stones
to the entry of the first trial.
Old ghost Duanmu,
are we inside the Ancient God's body ?
This is just an entrance,
a passage leading to the Ancient God's body.
It may be
just a single hair of the Ancient God.
Stop with your nonsense.
If this is just a single hair,
wouldn't the Ancient God's body
be larger than planet Suzaku ?
An adult Ancient God's body
is many times larger than planet Suzaku.
Then how long will it take to cross it ?
Where is the Ancient God's bag of holding ?
Ancient Gods didn't use bags of holding.
They kept their artifacts
hidden within their own bodies.
New guy,
since it's your first time in the Land of the Ancient God,
don't be too greedy.
Don't put on airs,
aren't we all here for the Soul Transformation Pills ?
You're not wrong,
our goal this time
is indeed the Soul Transformation Pills.
The rumors say that after completing all the trials,
they can be found within the Ancient God's meridians.
However...
we aren't here just for the Soul Transformation Pills.
Oh ?
What do you mean by that ?
There are countless treasures here.
Even though the Ancient God is dead,
his Divine Sense remains.
It's just in a dormant state.
If one can enter its body
and obtain its memories
then
any spell stored in its memory
would be incredibly powerful
in the present day and age.
These Soul Formation Devil Lords
came here before but failed to pass the trials
and spent a 1000 years preparing for this trip.
It shows how dangerous this place is...
I must find a way to escape quickly...
What are these stars ?
Why is my Ji Realm so restless ?
Kid,
don't overthink it.
Try not to provoke it,
it's been asleep for thousands of years.
It's just a beast,
it's not worth mentioning.
This is bad !
Des... A Desolate Beast...
What do we do ?
Flee !
Core Formation brat,
die in my place !
Fear !
Six Desires brat,
what are you doing !?
This Desolate Beast is too fast,
so you will delay it for me.
How dare you !?
An Early stage Soul Formation
should be glad to die in my stead.
The entrance to the first trial is right ahead,
Everyone,
don't hold back now !
Fear !
Whether the Eight Extremes Devil Lord wins or loses,
I have no way out...
Note: 1 zhang = 1m
A Flood Dragon over a 1000 zhang long
possesses various innate abilities
and is astonishingly powerful.
If it's a Desolate Beast over 10 000 zhang long,
its innate abilities will be even more powerful.
Even legendary Soul Formation cultivators can't resist it.
Middle stage Soul Formation
against a Peak Late stage Soul Formation Desolate Beast
should have no chance at all.
But why isn't the Desolate Beast using spells ?
Is something wrong here ?
So that's why !
Let's go !
As expected of Master !
With a single glance
you saw that this dragon's belly was the safest place !
Once the Devil Lords are gone,
we can get out !
I was right, something was wrong.
The outside is just a dead body
and the true dragon was inside.
So it's not a true Desolate Beast
but a parasite in a Desolate Beast's corpse.
Since that's the case,
I can kill it !
Wan'er told me
the true treasure of a Flood Dragon is not its core
but its marrow.
It's gone...
I shouldn't stay here.
This is...
Why is it completely ineffective ?
There's a beast in the void
that's intelligent.
And there is more than one...
It seems I can't bypass them.
15 days later
Crossing a few hundred zhang
took me 15 days.
I'm out of artifacts.
If I stay here any longer,
it will lead to my death.
A spatial rift opens and closes in half a breath.
I can fly to the teleportation formation in less than half a breath,
then this is the last step
and my last chance.
It's her...
Senior...
This is for you.
Senior,
The cultivation path is extremely dangerous
but I hope that if you encounter danger in the future,
this formation can delay it for a moment.
If it helps you,
Wan'er will be satisfied.
Thank you.
If this passage is so dangerous
then the trials must be unimaginably difficult.
If I take a wrong step
with my current cultivation,
I will die for sure.
I need to leave this place at once.
This shape is...
top-quality spirit stones ?
As expected,
my regular spirit stones are useless.
But Duanmu Ji came here last time
and was able to leave halfway.
That means he has another way out.
Let's not overthink this.
In that case,
I just need to pass the trials !
Think of "Spirit Beasts" and "Desolate Beasts" as cultivation levels for beasts.
Count the specks of time
floating down gently.
The carving knife in your hands etches out destiny.
Forever lock away the scars
of this mortal life.
This fleeting youth is a thing of the past.
The flying bird could not escape the twilight
that fills the sky with a myriad of colors.
The night-blooming flower cannot drink
the crystalization of the golden wind and the jade dew.
I will ask the heavens who exactly
sliced open this world
to let the rain fall in.
I will refine the world
to make our palm lines say
that we will live forever.
Walking off the beaten path
through heaven and earth.
Before returning to dust,
I will refine this mortal body.
The left shore is the joyous laughter
that can brighten up a thousand years of sadness.
The right shore is an eternal silence
lingering under the candlelight.
To overturn this fate,
I will walk against the heavens.
I will even gather the clouds
to illuminate the sky for you.
All this sadness was not meaningless.
How many lives and deaths\Nhave passed in the blink of an eye ?
I vow to break
this chess game of fate.